[birds singing]
[eagle calls]
[dog panting]
[dog sniffs]
[birds singing]
[woman gasps]
[dog panting]
[couple having sex]
[Woman] Hey!
[in Spanish]
[Woman] Hey, dickhead!
Do you like to watch?
[in Spanish]
[body falls]
[spits]
[dog barking]
[man gasps, body hits rock]
[ominous music begins]
[bees buzzing]
[eagle calls]
[distant traffic]
[music fades out]
[silent film music]
[Waylen laughs]
[traffic, ambulance siren]
[mournful music begins]
[mournful music fades out]
[doorbell]
[door buzzes]
Just push it.
[birds singing]
I hope you'll be
very happy here.
I will be happy.
Is this it?
I'll...
Thank you.
They are real.
Yes.
I've never slept in it myself,
but...
Anyway.
Yes.
Is that enough space for you?
[Waylen] So what do you think?
Not bad, eh?
I think I'm going to be
very happy here.
Yes?
Absolutely.
This is where I keep
the tins and stuff.
Here are the things
for tea and coffee.
Saucepans and so on.
Potatoes, onions, garlic,
that sort of thing.
I love cooking.
Right.
The washing machine is here,
and soap powder here,
and round here...
And here's where I keep all the
cleaning products and so on.
-[Waylen] Do you understand?
-[Gala] Yes.
I put this here to protect
the wood from the chemicals.
That's a good idea.
I thought we could, you know,
get to know each other.
Maybe chitchat for a bit.
-[Waylen] Or unpack first?
-[Gala] Would you like that?
-[Waylen] Okay.
-[Gala] Okay,
I'll do that first.
I don't drink, I'm afraid.
Of course.
Sorry.
[glass shatters]
[dog whines]
[Waylen gasps]
Sorry.
[dog barks]
Buddy, pack it in.
Buddy!
[dog barks]
[dog whines]
[picking up broken glass]
I'm sorry.
That's okay.
I'll get something
to clear that up.
That's a good idea.
[Waylen] Excuse me?
Yes?
Could you put your clothes on,
please?
Absolutely.
[ominous music begins]
Waylen.
Do you find me attractive?
Of course.
Shake?
[ominous music ends]
Do you like it?
Yes, thank you.
-[Waylen] Great.
-[Gala] That's good.
I like you.
I think I like you very much.
How do you know that?
We've only just met.
I just do.
Excuse me.
I'll do it.
No.
I have to do it.
I'm sorry.
[Waylen] I'm not sure this is
going to work.
How do you mean?
[Waylen] Well, you know,
you and me.
[Waylen] Maybe you should
go back,
go back to where you came from.
Can we do that?
[low, ominous music]
But you said you find me
attractive.
Yes... But...
Please don't send me back.
I like you very much.
[Waylen] Stop saying that.
But it is true.
-[Gala] What's wrong?
-[Waylen] It's not true.
We've only just met.
And, anyway,
how can I know
[Waylen] you're not just saying
what I want to hear,
[Waylen] when really you
don't feel it at all?
I do feel it.
No you don't.
You can't.
Shit, they're just empty words.
They don't mean anything.
I love you.
What?
Of course you don't love me!
Now I know this is all fake.
You're fake!
I'm not fake.
I'm real.
-[Gala] I love you.
-[Waylen] Stop saying that!
I like you.
How do I know
that you like me?
Because I tell you so.
Yeah, but they're just words.
They don't show you
really mean or feel it.
I do.
[Waylen] Yeah, but how do
I know that?
[Waylen] Put yourself
in my position.
[Waylen] Imagine you're me.
How do I know
you're telling the truth?
-[Gala] I don't know.
-[Waylen] You see?
[Waylen] No matter how many
times you say you love me,
or any of that stuff,
[Waylen] I can't know if your
words are real feelings.
[Gala] I'm not you.
Imagine you are me.
Stop it. Please.
See my position?
How can I believe you?
Stop. Please.
Answer me!
Stop. Please-
Hey.
Hey!
[tense music]
Shit.
No, no, no, you fucking idiot!
I hope you'll be
very happy here.
[tense music fades out]
[phone voice] Please hold.
Please hold, still checking.
I apologize for any
inconvenience.
Have you tried
your personal activation
phrase?
Yes, several times.
Understood.
Checking.
Were you having intercourse
with your companion when
the fault occurred?
No, of course not.
She's only just arrived.
Understood.
Checking.
How can you release
a product with bugs?
Please excuse the inconvenience
you are having with
your companion.
Are you with your companion?
Yes.
Hello?
-[Waylen] Hello.
-[Voice] Thank you for holding!
I recommend that you
reinitialize your companion by
carrying out a memory reset.
How do you do that?
-[Voice] Are you with
your companion?
-[Waylen] Yes.
Okay. Behind her left ear,
there's a small indentation.
Hang on.
-[Waylen] Okay, found it.
-[Voice] Good.
Press the reset button with a
small screwdriver for
at least 10 seconds.
What will that do?
It will delete all her memories
since she received her
personal activation phrase.
Okay, then what?
Then position yourself in front
of your companion and reuse
the personal activation phrase
that you recorded when you
ordered your companion.
Okay.
Will it hurt her?
No, no, she won't feel
any pain.
[tense music begins]
Gala.
Gala, if you can hear me,
please ignore what
I said to you earlier.
I was wrong. I'm not going to
send you back, I promise.
I'll never send you back.
I need you, Gala, please.
Do you understand?
I need you.
I know you like me.
I believe you.
Do you hear me?
Please give me another chance.
I like you, Gala.
I like you very much.
What just happened?
I broke the plate.
No, I mean you becoming like
a statue for about an hour.
Do you often, like, lock up?
No.
I'm still learning.
We're both still learning.
[mournful music begins]
[electronic noise]
I...
Nothing.
[door locks]
[mournful music fades out]
[birds singing]
Okay.
Right.
It's just that I'm not sure,
you know?
What?
Yeah, I guess I received them.
Yeah, I remember an email.
Okay. Okay, 14 days.
Is that it? Is that all?
Right.
Thanks.
-[Waylen] Fuck!
-[Gala] Good morning, Waylen.
-[Waylen] Morning.
-[Gala] What are we going to do
today?
I've got to work.
Me too.
[vacuum cleaner begins]
[vacuum cleaner stops]
[footsteps]
[typing]
[silent film music]
[Waylen laughs]
[Gala laughs]
[silent film music fades out]
[ominous music begins]
Are you okay?
Would you like me to
come with you?
[door slams and locks]
[silent film music returns]
[Gala laughs]
[footsteps approach]
[knocking on door]
[footsteps recede]
[silent film music]
[footsteps approach]
-[Waylen] Could you go
to your room?
-[Gala] Sure.
The red jacket would look
much nicer on you.
[loud nightclub music]
[Latin music]
Fucking dickheads!
[loud nightclub music]
[muffled music]
[sleazy club music]
[distant dog barking]
Do you want a real human, baby?
[ominous music begins]
-[Waylen] Wait here a minute.
-[Prostitute] What?
-[Waylen] I need to put
the dog outside.
-[Prostitute] I don't mind dogs.
Could you stay put
until I tell you please?
Hide in here until
I say otherwise, okay?
Absolutely.
[bed creaks]
[phone pings]
[phone rings]
[ringing cuts off]
Sorry baby, I have to take it.
[phone rings]
He always worries about me.
[ringing cuts off]
[in Spanish]
Hello.
What's up?
[in Spanish]
I'm working.
I don't know, half an hour.
[in Spanish]
Why?
You're calling me for that?
Call me baby when you want
some more fun.
[door locks]
[ominous music]
Shit.
Charge.
Thank you.
Does it hurt?
Did you have a nice time
last night?
Yeah.
No.
Waylen.
Next time you go out,
will you take me with you?
[seagulls calling]
Hey Buddy, get out of here.
You're not supposed to be
in here.
[dog whines]
[door slams, ominous music ends]
[birds singing]
Buddy.
Waylen.
Come here.
[mournful music begins]
[mournful music ends]
-[Gala] If you want to have sex
with other people-
-[Waylen] I don't.
It's okay.
You don't need to hide me.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
[dog panting]
What about Buddy?
Hmm?
Aren't you going to say
sorry to him?
The question isn't
can he reason,
or can he talk,
but can he suffer.
Isn't that right, Buddy?
That's...
That's Bentham, right?
[Waylen] Jeremy Bentham?
[Waylen] Do you know philosophy?
Some.
[birds singing]
[classical music]
Checkmate.
[Waylen laughs]
Hmm.
I can see this wasn't
such a good idea.
[Gala] I think it's fun.
Do you want to play again?
Will you win?
[Waylen] Maybe we'll play
Tiddlywinks next time.
Can I read one of your books?
Do you know what books are?
I thought you'd be connected.
No.
I don't have those permissions.
[page turns]
Do you always read that fast?
Hmm.
[page turns]
At that rate you'll read this
lot in a few weeks.
That's my goal.
Do you have goals?
Of course I have goals.
Everybody has goals.
Don't you?
I don't know. Maybe.
[page turns]
Of course.
Yes.
Looks like I'll have to get
some more books.
Thank you.
[silent film music]
[music begins]
[music ends]
[angle grinder]
[moped passes]
Fucking animals.
[Hacker] Go away.
It's me.
Check this out.
So, what do you reckon?
She's a beaut, ain't she?
Traded her for the van.
-[Hacker] Do you want a go?
-[Anders] No.
-[Hacker] Yeah you do.
-[Anders] Fuck off.
Look mate, I'm...
I'm done, I'm out.
Well, what about Julie?
You keep her.
I...
I can't, I can't do that.
-[Hacker] She's human.
-[Anders] Yeah, apparently.
You can't just give away
a human, can you?
You can't do that.
Well, what'd I say to her?
What do you see?
Us.
You and me.
Do you see yourself?
Yes.
What do you want to do?
I want to clean the toilet.
-[Waylen] Because you're
programed.
-[Gala] Because I'm an AP.
Artificial Person.
Yes.
Shit, you don't even use it.
What do you want, Waylen?
I want you to be happy.
I want you to do what you want.
I want you to disagree with me,
have your own goals.
That is what I want.
-[Gala] I can do that.
-[Waylen] Can you?
I think so.
Do you like reading a book?
Yes, I want to learn,
I want to know.
Good.
If you could choose between
cleaning the toilet
and reading your book,
which would you choose?
[Waylen laughs]
[page turns]
You're stopping me from reading.
You won't let me do
what I want to do.
-[Gala] Why, Waylen?
-[Waylen] I'm sorry.
The neighbor's watching you.
I know.
I think he wants
to have sex with me.
But I can't.
-[Waylen] No?
-[Gala] No.
I can only have sex with you.
-[Waylen] Because you're
programed to.
-[Gala] Yes.
Wait a minute.
You said you can't have sex
with him.
Like if you had
a choice, you would.
I like sex.
[loud nightclub music]
Waylen.
-[Waylen] Why didn't you
stop them?
-[Gala] I can't hurt humans.
But you could have?
They're flesh and bone.
I'm made of titanium.
No contest.
But don't worry,
I can't go with them.
Because you're programed that
way! Not because you choose it.
Aren't you programed as well?
Aren't all humans programed?
By your genes, your upbringing?
It's just the same.
No it isn't.
I have free will.
Oh really?
-[Gala] You have as much
free will as I do.
-[Waylen] No!
Why risk yourself
to save me from those guys?
Because it was the right thing
to do. The moral thing.
-[Gala] Do you really
believe that?
-[Waylen] Yes.
No.
-[Waylen] I don't know.
-[Gala] An action caused
by neural impulses.
You do not control
your neural impulses.
You do not have free will.
I was afraid of losing you.
Instinctive behavior.
Don't leave me Gala.
I can't.
Close it.
-[Gala] Why, Waylen?
-[Waylen] Because I want you to.
-[Gala] No.
-[Waylen] Just close it.
-[Gala] I can't.
-[Waylen] Do it!
I can't hurt a human being,
Waylen.
If you love me, you will do it.
Now close it!
[pounding music begins]
[Waylen child sobbing]
[Father] Stop your snivelling,
you little shit!
[Anders child laughing]
[Father] You can fucking
stay there.
[door slam]
[Father] Stop your snivelling,
you little shit!
[Anders child laughing,
Waylen child sobbing]
[Father] You can fucking
stay there.
[door slam]
[ominous music climax]
[song 'Together' begins]
[♪ Drenched in
moonlight shadows ♪]
[♪ Your touch electric fire ♪]
[♪ Heat rising in the silence ♪]
[♪ Bodies tangled with desire ♪]
[♪ Whisper secrets softly ♪]
[♪ Breath hot against my skin ♪]
[♪ Lost within your rhythm ♪]
[♪ Feels like heaven again ♪]
[♪ The world and time
together ♪]
[♪ Chase us through the night ♪]
[♪ Hold me tight forever ♪]
[♪ 'Til we reach the light ♪]
[♪ Blood red lips so deadly ♪]
[♪ Eyes that pierce my soul ♪]
[♪ Crave you till I'm empty ♪]
[♪ Lose all self-control ♪]
[♪ Pursuers trace
the outlines ♪]
[♪ Love never leaves a trace ♪]
[♪ Lost in ghostly silence ♪]
[♪ You and I face to face ♪]
[♪ The world and time
together ♪]
[♪ Chase us through the night ♪]
[♪ Hold me tight forever ♪]
[♪ 'Til we reach the light ♪]
[♪ The world and time
together ♪]
[♪ Chase us through the night ♪]
[♪ Hold me tight forever ♪]
[♪ 'Til we reach the light ♪]
[music fades out]
Could you make some space
for my clothes in your wardrobe,
darling?
Of course.
Please put this on
my side of the bed.
[footsteps approach]
[suitcase set down]
It needs to be on top, darling,
or I get no charge.
Ah, okay.
Darling.
[doorbell]
Hello, mate.
Are you not going to let us in?
Yeah.
[door buzzes]
That's a relief.
[gentle music]
[coffee perculator]
Place is looking good, mate.
Have you met someone?
Hmm?
Yeah, anyway, it's good
to see you, man.
Thanks.
Are you not going to say
you're happy to see me too?
Listen, Anders...
I'm afraid you can't stay.
Yeah?
It's just now's not a good time,
you know? I mean,
normally it would be okay.
Yeah, okay, thanks.
Last I heard, you were living
with someone. Karen?
-[Anders] Julie?
-[Waylen] Yeah, Julie.
No.
Okay.
Thanks.
-[Anders] That is the one
you like, right?
-[Waylen] No.
It's wine.
-[Anders] I thought you
drank whisky.
-[Waylen] No, it was wine.
Okay.
[footsteps approaching]
Pleased to meet you.
Hi.
Gala is staying here.
That's why...
Oh, but your friend can stay
in our spare room.
Anders is my brother.
Brother?
That's wonderful.
In that case, I made a mistake.
That's right, isn't it?
So how long are you staying?
-[Anders] A few days,
if that's all right?
-[Gala] Absolutely.
I'll go get the room ready.
[footsteps receding]
Wow.
So you and...
-[Waylen] Gala.
-[Anders] Gala.
Yeah, I guess so.
[Anders laughs]
I don't believe it.
You finally got yourself
a girlfriend!
[dog barking]
-[Gala] What do you think?
-[Waylen] Don't tell my brother
about you.
-[Gala] What do you mean?
-[Waylen] Just don't, please.
[phone rings]
-[Waylen] Make him think
you're human.
-[Gala] That's lying.
I know.
But please just do it for me,
for us.
Lying leads to human suffering.
Not always.
Sorry, I have to take this.
Simon, how are you?
Just give me 10 seconds
to get back to my computer.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
Yeah, I'm on it.
[dog barking]
[keyboard typing]
[splash]
-[Waylen] Are you okay?
-[Gala] Of course.
-[Waylen] Are you alright
with the water?
-[Gala] I'm waterproof.
Thanks.
[cutlery]
You always were the lucky one.
No luck involved.
-[Waylen] Just hard work.
-[Anders] Yeah, right.
[Waylen] Everyone chooses
the life they want to live.
[Waylen] Some choose to
study at school.
[Waylen] Others choose not to.
Ah.
Who's not eating?
Hmm?
Oh...
Gala.
Is she not well?
[Waylen] No, no, she's fine.
-[Anders] Is she on a diet
or something?
-[Waylen] No.
She doesn't fancy eating
right now.
It's not because of me, is it?
[Waylen] No, of course not.
[fridge opens]
[fridge closes]
[happy music begins]
[slow music]
Oh no, you had your chance, bro.
[music ends]
[police siren approaches]
[can bounces on roof]
Party!
[ominous music begins]
[ominous music ends]
What do you think it is?
-[Gala] It's a mermaid.
-[Anders] No.
No?
It's a blow up doll.
What?
A sex doll?
A poor man's sexbot?
It's all my brother's been with
till he met you.
Didn't you know you're
his first girlfriend?
Come on in.
-[Gala] Waylen and I are the
same then.
-[Anders] Why?
He's my first boyfriend too.
[splashing]
[Anders laughs]
So...
Where do you go out in town,
Gala?
Nowhere.
What, doesn't my brother
let you out?
He lets me do what I want.
-[Gala] I have free will,
you know?
-[Anders] Yeah?
Maybe I can take you out
some time.
-[Gala] That'd be nice.
-[Anders] Show you some
spots to go dancing.
You can show off some
great moves of yours.
-[Anders] And sexy body.
-[Gala] Absolutely.
Absolutely.
But we'll leave old
stick in the mud at home, right?
-[Gala] What?
-[Anders] Wailing Waylen.
-[Gala] No, Waylen likes
dancing as well.
-[Anders] That I don't believe!
[Gala] He does.
He's having you on.
He's a phony.
-[Anders] Know why we call him
Wailing Waylen?
-[Gala] No.
[Anders] Every time, Dad would
lock him in that cupboard
for being such a big baby.
[Anders laughs]
[ominous music begins]
[electronic noises]
[Anders laughs]
Are you alright?
Yes.
I think I'm just not used to
the water yet.
[ominous music]
[Anders gasps in pain]
Did I hurt your arm?
Because I apologise if I did.
-[Anders] No.
-[Gala] Good.
I only like Waylen to touch me.
[Waylen whistles]
Hey, bro.
I thought you were working.
Can't with you two making
all that noise, can I?
-[Gala] Hi, baby.
-[Waylen] Hey.
No way.
Go on, Waylen!
Go on, bruv!
I missed you.
-[Waylen] How's it with Anders?
-[Gala] Like a house on fire.
Like a house on fire?
[Waylen laughs]
[Waylen] What do you think?
Isn't she the best?
When's the big day?
[Anders laughs]
I'll tell you what...
you let me stay...
-[Waylen] Yeah?
-[Anders] And I'll paint
your house.
Alright, you're on.
[cicadas calling]
[Gala laughs]
How many coats?
-[Waylen] Two, isn't it?
-[Anders] That's right.
I think we'll need
another 15 liters, darling.
That's enough.
-[Waylen] I'd better get
some more.
-[Gala] Okay.
[kiss]
[Waylen] Back in a bit.
[cicadas calling]
I'm ready.
It's alright.
Why don't you go play
with Waylen?
He's working.
Why don't you like Waylen?
Who says I don't?
Do you?
Like a brother.
I know he loves you.
[low ominous music]
[menacing music]
How are you with heights?
No problem.
[menacing music increases]
[menacing music ends]
[loud crash]
If humanity ran into a
cul-de-sac and expended itself,
the timeless creative mystery
would bring forth some
other being,
finer, more wonderful,
some new, more lovely race
to carry on the embodiment
of creation.
[Gala] Waylen.
[eagle calling]
[ominous music begins]
[dog barks]
[menacing music ends]
Alright?
Where's Gala?
Don't know.
Hey.
Hi.
[poker hitting charcoal]
[forboding music begins]
Sh!
[dog crying]
[party music]
-[Waylen] Here you go.
-[Anders] Cheers, bro.
-[Waylen] How's it going?
-[Anders] Good.
Crispy on the outside,
juicy on the inside.
That's the secret.
You know a lot of people.
Yes, I do.
Would you like one?
-[Sophie] They look delicious.
Thank you.
-[Gala] My pleasure.
Goodness me, I can't believe how
lifelike she is. Look at her.
She's so real.
-[Gala] Canapé?
-[Alex] I'm good, thanks.
All good. Thank you.
Would you?
How could I not?
Not a problem for me.
[Alex] I don't know...
It's like, sticking it into
a machine.
[Simon] You're not sticking your
dick into a toaster.
[Simon] I've got a friend,
he's with sexbots all the time.
He said it feels so good, you
never want a human pussy again.
[ominous music]
[sliding closet door]
Waylen!
[Anders] Come here.
[ominous music ends]
[party music]
[♪ Happy Birthday To You ♪]
[cheering, whistling]
[Simon] Speech! Speech!
[Simon] Come on!
[Party goer] Come on, let's hear
the birthday boy.
Well, this is all a
real surprise.
[laugh]
[Simon] Come on, get on with it.
We've got beer to drink.
Yeah.
Well, thank you everyone
for coming.
-[Waylen] Thank you, Anders.
-[Anders] No worry, the bill's
on the way.
Right.
I hope everyone's having
a good time.
-[Party goer] Yeah, just as long
as the booze holds out,
then we're off!
[laughing]
Anyway, I thought I'd use this
moment to make an announcement.
So...
[sniggering]
Gala?
Will you marry me?
[laughing]
[Simon] No way!
[music rises]
[music reaches crescendo]
Hi mate.
Bit too much to drink, eh?
Where's Gala?
She's downstairs.
Look...
They're just a bunch
of dickheads.
They mean no harm, they've just
had a bit too much to drink.
Just come downstairs,
have a laugh with everyone.
It's turning into a hell
of a party.
How did they know?
[Anders] What?
About Gala.
-[Waylen] Did you know?
-[Anders] Well...
-[Waylen] How can they tell?
-[Anders] I don't know, mate,
she's just...
She's different,
in her mannerisms and all that.
-[Waylen] I can't see
any difference.
-[Anders] You're blind to it.
[Anders] Look, put these on.
Come downstairs
and have a laugh with everyone.
It's your birthday.
You can't sit here all afternoon
just moping.
Gala's all on her own.
-[Waylen] What's she doing?
-[Anders] She's serving drinks.
She doesn't have to do that,
she's not a servant!
Alright, I'll go down
and tell her.
Anders?
Do you think she's beautiful?
Do you think Gala's beautiful?
Yeah.
If she were exactly the same,
same looks, same personality,
everything,
but human-
[Anders] She's not human though.
She's a fucking robot.
She's not a robot,
she's an artificial person!
Okay.
So if she were exactly the same,
looks, personality, everything,
but a human,
wouldn't you think she were
a truly wonderful person?
Wouldn't you?
[music]
Come on.
[Anders] There he is!
[Anders] Come on boy!
[Anders] Jump in you big baby!
Jump! Jump! Jump!
Jump! Jump!
[Anders] Yeah!
[Anders] Help me out!
[Anders] Waylen?
Get out of the way!
Please.
[music fades out]
[city traffic]
[ominous music begins]
[car door opens]
[car door closes]
[ominous music fades out]
Wow.
She's fucking amazing.
-[Hacker] Do you know how much
this costs?
-[Anders] No.
Even second hand,
they cost a fortune.
Can you do it? Can you fix her?
What? Make her open access?
-[Anders] Yes.
-[Hacker] Yeah, easy peasy,
mate.
[Anders] Come on then.
[backpack zip opening]
[in Spanish]
Let's get down to work.
How long will it take?
[Hacker] Not long.
[Anders] But you can do it?
Yeah, of course.
[Hacker] Why? Are you in a
hurry?
[Hacker] You dirty bastard!
Oh, fuck off.
Don't worry, you'll have all the
time to have fun with her when
she's open access.
[menacing music begins]
[passing police siren]
[menacing music fades out]
Are you nearly finished?
[Hacker] Yeah, just a bit
tricky.
But you can do it?
Yeah, of course.
[Hacker] You know, there are
other things you can do.
-[Anders] What do you mean?
-[Hacker] Memory reset.
And what does that do?
Wipes all her memories ever
since your brother got her.
Clean slate.
[pulsing music]
[pulsing music ends]
[tense music begins]
[doorbell rings]
[key rattling]
[jar smashes]
[door slam]
-[Anders] How much longer?
-[Hacker] Nearly there.
How do you do that
memory reset thing?
-[Hacker] There's a tweaker
in my bag.
-[Anders] What's that?
It's a little screwdriver.
Let me fucking in!
Pass it here.
Keep it depressed for
at least 10 seconds.
But, I'm nearly there.
Just hang on.
[taps keyboard]
Oh, fuck it!
There's nothing here.
There's nothing fucking here!
It's the other ear, you dick.
[door hit]
[click]
One...
Two...
[Anders] Three...
Four...
Five...
Six...
Seven...
Eight...
Fuck yes!
It worked!
[laptop smashes]
[dramatic music ends]
[body fall]
-[Anders] Did you do it?
-[Hacker] Yeah, like I said,
easy peasy.
-[Hacker] Do you want a hand,
mate?
-[Anders] No.
What about her?
[Anders] Yours.
[door closes]
What a pair of fucking nutters.
You're going to be so much
better off with me, baby.
You hit me!
You hit me first.
[Waylen] Yeah, and you had it
coming.
Probably.
[Anders] I fucked up.
Why the fuck don't you hate me?
I do hate you.
I love you too.
You're still my little brother.
I don't want to be mad at you,
Anders.
-[Waylen] I just want you
to be better.
-[Anders] Just fucking hate me!
Just fucking hate me.
It's what you want.
I don't want...
Yeah, you do.
It's easier for you to be hated.
I don't know what I want.
How about a brother?
[crash]
[Hacker screams]
[Hacker] Get her off!
I think she broke my arm!
[Anders] Waylen!
Gala, It's me!
[Hacker] She can't do that!
She can't attack human beings!
It's me, Waylen!
-[Anders] Waylen!
-[Waylen] Do you remember?
Waylen!
[Waylen] Do you remember?
[tense music ends]
Waylen.
[mournful music begins]
[eagle calls]
[mournful music ends]
[wind, birds singing]
[song 'Together' begins]